United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records 5810
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records
1928-1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC)
5810
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5710644
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 05, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, often referred to as the United Brotherhood of Carpenters was formed in 1881. It has grown to be one of the largest trade unions in the United States, and between its chapters and locals there is international cooperation. Local 125 is based in Utica, New York.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5278: Utica Trades Assembly Records 5288: International Brotherhood Pulp, Sulphite, Paper Mill Workers, Local 670 (Utica, NY) Minute Book 5718: Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Documents 5718 mf: Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Documents on Microfilm 5818 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 662 (Mt. Morris, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5822 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Rochester, NY. Records on Microfilm 5810: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records 5810 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records on Microfilm 5811: International Typographical Union Local 62 (Utica, NY) Minute Book 5819 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1508 (Lyons, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5820 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 240 (East Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5821 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 72 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5826: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books 5826 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5827: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books 5827 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books on Microfilm 5828: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books 5828 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5829: Utica, NY, Building Trades Council Minute Books 5829 mf: Utica, NY, Building Trades Council Minute Books on Microfilm 5686 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners. Local 187 (Geneva, NY) Records on Microfilm
Carpenters--Labor unions--New York (State)--Utica.; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America.; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Local 125 (Utica, N.Y.)
5710644
- Minute books 1891-1970 (12 volumes) (Box 1)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125 Utica, NY, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Minute book Vol.12 - 3/4/1964 - 10/21/1970
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125 Utica, NY, 1958-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Vol. 11 - 4/16/1958 - 2/19/1964
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125 Utica, NY Minute book, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Vol. 1 - 6/20/1891 - 2/14/1894
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125 Utica, NY, 1903-1904 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Minute book Vol.2 - 7/22/1903 - 12/28/1904
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125 Utica, NY Minute book, 1891-1894 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Vol.1 - 6/20/1891 - 2/14/1894
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125 Utica, NY Minute book, 1903-1904 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Vol.2 - 7/22/1903 - 12/28/1904
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125 Utica, NY Minute book, 1905-1906 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Vol. 3 - 1/4/1905 - 7/5/1906
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125, Utica, NY, 1906-1908 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Minute book Vol.4 - 7/11/1906 - 3/11/1908
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125, Utica, NY Minute book, 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Vol. 5 - 8/13/1919 - 11/30/1921
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125, Utica, NY Minute book, 1921-1924 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Vol. 6 - 12/7/1921 - 5/14/1924
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125, Utica, NY Minute book, 1924-1927 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Vol. 7 - 5/21/1924 - 6/15/1927
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125, Utica, NY Minute book, 1944-1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Vol. 9 - 1/5/1944 - 1/4/1950
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 125, Utica, NY Minute book, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Vol. 10 - 1/18/1950 - 5/5/1954
- Ledger Books. (Box 2)
  - Ledger of Trustees U.B. of C&J Local Union 125 Utica, NY (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ledger U.B. of C&J Local Union 125 Utica, NY (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ledger of Trustees U.B. of C&J Local Union 125 Utica, NY (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Ledger Books. (Box 3)
  - Record, 1891-1893 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    1891,1892,1893
  - Record, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    1973-1974
  - Record, 1888-1890 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    1888,1889,1890
  - Record (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Record, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    1903
  - Record, 1894-1896 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    1894,1895,1896
  - Record, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    1932,1933
  - Ledger (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Ledger Books. (Box 4)
  - Record, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    1962
  - Record, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    1913
  - Record, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    1902
  - Record, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    1920
  - Record, 1897-1898 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    1897,1898
  - Record, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    1907
  - Record, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    1917
  - Record, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    1916
  - Record, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Ledger Books. (Box 5)
  - Ledger, 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    1930,1931
  - Record, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    1947,1948
  - Day Book - Carpenter's Local No. 125, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Record, 1912-1913 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    1912,1913
  - Ledger, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    1901
  - Ledger, 1910-1918 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    1910,1919,1915,1917,1918
  - Record, 1917-1921 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    1917,1921
  - Record, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Ledger Books. (Box 6)
  - Record, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Record, 1899-1900 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Record, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    1940,1941,1943
  - Suspended- C. Cords Members (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Record (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Minute book Local Union No. M.V.D.C. Utica, NY (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Union Photographs (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Ledger Books. (Box 7)
  - Record, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    1969
  - Ledger (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ledger, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    1934,1935
  - Ledger (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ledger, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    1942,1943
  - Ledger, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    1936,1937
  - Ledger, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    1919
  - Ledger, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    1915
  - Ledger, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    1910
  - Ledger, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    1905
  - Ledger (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ledger (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ledger, 1945-1947 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    1945,1946,1947
  - Ledger, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    August 15,1911 Board of Trustees Local #125
  - Ledger, U.B. of C&J Local Union 125 Utica, NY (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Ledger Books. (Box 8)
  - Ledger, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ledger, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    1912
  - Ledger, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Ledger (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ledger, 1945-1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    1945-1946-1947
  - Ledger (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ledger U.B. of C & J of A Local Union 125, Utica, NY, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Ledger Books. (Box 9)
  - Ledger (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ledger (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Ledger Books. (Box 10)
  - Ledger, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    1918
  - Ledger, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    1921
  - Ledger, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    1923
  - Ledger, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    1911
  - Ledger, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    1938-1939
  - Ledger, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Ledger Books. (Box 11)
  - Ledger, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    to January 1947 to Treasurer
  - Ledger, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    1931
  - Ledger (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ledger, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Ledger (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ledger (Box 11, Folder 6)
    E-K
  - Ledger (Box 11, Folder 7)
    R-Z